<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Value CoCreator]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Value CoCreator]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/valuecocreator/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2016 10:43:38 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/valuecocreator/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[WE TRANSFORM SALES ORGANISATON FROM SELLING TO COCREATING VALUE]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>WE TRANSFORM SALES ORGANISATON FROM SELLING TO COCREATING VALUE</h1><p>We transform sales organisations from Selling Value to Co-Creating Value with their customers. </p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/d2b87eae27c8980539c3e0c2b6a3bc6ab2a91960.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/valuecocreator/we-transform-sales-organisaton-from-selling-to-cocreating-va/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">808b71bd-01ed-449f-bb3c-ca1a878720a2</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2016 09:56:01 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Book]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The Book</h1><p>Read our book on the new trends in sales and how to prepare yourself to co-create value with your customers. </p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/704bce66b25db165094f94661ca925fafc4dbec6.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>urn:uuid:52e5ae45-b0c2-4451-b7d3-216dee964512</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">eccddb41-752d-414d-bb58-39dce9a69677</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2016 10:42:59 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Co-Creation and Design Thinking in Sales]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Co-Creation and Design Thinking in Sales</h1><p>This course brings you the latest best practices on how to create value with your customers and new business opportunities. In a market, where products and services are rapidly becoming commodities and where customers demand greater added value and better prices, the conventional approach to selling has to be revised. Now, a new approach to develop business opportunities with customer is needed based on co-creating value rather than on selling value. Sales people have to become much more strategic in their approach focussing on helping customer to achieve their business outcomes based on close and deep collaboration between their organisation and their customers.  What is this program about?  During the first day the participants will learn how they can engage customers and Co-Create Value with them rather then sell value to them. We will do this by playing a serious game on Co-Creation. The second day will focus on Design Thinking and how it can help you to design new services to co-creatie value with your customers. We will do this through a series of workshops where the participants will work on one of their own cases.  Who is this program for?  Sales and marketing managers who want to know more about the latest trends, tools and cases in business development Innovation managers who are looking for new innovative ways to engage and co-create value with their customers Sales executives who are looking for new proceses and tools to co-create value with their customers.  Why should you come? As a participant you will have the opportunity to:  Get to know the key trends and changes in sales now, rather than having to catch up later Get ahead of the competition by exploring new ways to further enhance your competitiveness by co-creating with rather then selling value to your customers Let yourself be inspired by a brand-new and unique program, based on a state-of-the-art research project conducted in the Benelux, UK and US Get the opportunity to network and exchange ideas with other practitioners in an exciting new field of expertise Put yourself into the shoes of a business developer and manage a co-creation projects Learn the soft skills you need to manage and lead a team of stakeholders through a co-creation process  What will you get out of it?  This workshop will teach you:  What value co-creation is and how it can help you to add more value to your customers How to use our tools and frameworks to co-create value with your customers What the different forms of co-creation in B2B sales are What the different sales methods are and when to use them Who will facilitate? Regis Lemmens, author of the book ‘From Selling to Co-Creating’. View Regis’ profile  Tim Schuurman, highly experienced trainer and facilitator with a background in Change Management and Business Modeling and co-founder of DT Academy. View Tim’s profile  What is the schedule? </p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/9469c306b16e84ea54a515c0e75638899f09c0eb.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/article/28th-29th-march-2016-co-creation-design-thinking-sales-r%25C3%25A9gis-lemmens/edit</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a89b60bc-e7aa-4575-b672-19451e96cba9</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2016 03:50:39 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sales 2020 : Regis Lemmens at TEDxLiege]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Sales 2020 : Regis Lemmens at TEDxLiege</h1><p>Régis Lemmens is a consultant, author and teacher on the topic of sales and sales management. He co-authored several articles and books including 'From Selling to Co-Creating' where he looks a the future of sales. He is a partner at Sales Cubes, a sales management consulting firm located in Belgium, that specialises in sales and key accounts management.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/768102dcdfdef7c5d893e8d89f6d9f3b82a515c3.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cYV9irrztIc</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">0fe0bfd3-1414-4a65-9e1d-6a1370ebf3e1</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2016 21:15:18 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/2e1e2c09-3e0b-49d3-91f1-cacd76f1a2d5.png">]]></description>
            <link>https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/2e1e2c09-3e0b-49d3-91f1-cacd76f1a2d5.png</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">500a6ad7-6524-49bd-94ff-a73f6d3a1fa2</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2016 13:10:43 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Stakeholder Analysis]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Stakeholder Analysis</h1><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/ad90575bc186d086cc8814a8cea9b6e28e189fc7.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/valuecocreator/stakeholder-analysis/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">b745e2de-5657-4520-9719-1eb1dba14db1</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2016 06:06:11 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Step into the shoes of a Co-Creator and play our Co-Creation game]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Step into the shoes of a Co-Creator and play our Co-Creation game</h1><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/36f9cefc1f79110bed0181a5fc09b5155cc0fbfb.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/valuecocreator/step-into-the-shoes-of-a-co-creator-and-play-our-co-creation/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">5b09d756-8fa1-4c0c-a758-4c2aaa0731cb</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2016 23:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>